LEI WANG



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Results-driven change agent with career-long record of operations, client relationship management and inventory management for leading organizations

Proven talent for aligning business strategy and objectives with established retail and operations management paradigms to achieve maximum operational impacts with minimum resource expenditures. Growth-focused thought leader with expertise spanning inventory management, client relationship management, data and analysis, technology solutions and project management. Exceptionally dedicated professional with keen interpersonal, communication, and organizational skills, as well as budget management, policy development, and resource allocation expertise.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SUNNY GROUP(AUST) P/L, DANDENONG STH, May 2019 - Current

COORDINATER(WAREHOUSE)

- Unloading the products from containers or trucks and check to ensure that they match with the packing documents such as the bill of lading, shipping invoice or delivery note.
- Picking the goods for dispatch from their various storage locations and assembles them before verifying that they are in good condition and may be shipped to the customer.
- Operating equipments, including hi-reach forklift, order picker forklift, counter balance forklift and all sorts of electronic tools (to modify goods when needed).
- Delivery goods to customers, predominately plumbing shops around metro Melbourne.
- Inventory control, report to general manager regarding any stock availability issue.

CHOICE BATHROOMS & KITCHEN SUPPLIES, SPRINGVALE, April 2014 – March 2019

SHOWROOM CONSULTANT/ WAREHOUSE STOREPERSON

- Demonstrate excellent customer service, showing products, offering recommendations, fulfilling requests, answering inquiries, etc. for bathroom and kitchen products including appliances
- Navigate creation, tracking and fulfillment of customer orders with Reckon Quickbook
- Spearhead daily operations such as preparing quotations, coordinating accounts payable and credit data with Excel, etc.
- Oversaw warehouse duties, checking and allocating inward goods and collating and delivering outward goods
- Align objectives with various importers, manufacturers, courier/logistics companies to facilitate efficient operations and build strong partnerships
- Pioneered management of company website and online shop, to maximizing company exposure online and gaining extra profit

HILL STREET GROCER, HOBART, June 2011 - January 2014

FRESH PRODUCE RETAIL ASSISTANT

- Directed inventory efforts, unloading goods, rotating stock, monitoring items, and placing orders
- Conducted fulfillment of customer orders, picking, packing and dispatching goods
- Established processes to ensure organization, cleanliness and safety in the warehouse
- Liaised with customers, answering inquiries, fulfilling requests, directing phone calls

LEI WANG Page 2

ANGELICARE TASMANIA, HOBART, March 2011 – August 2012

AGED CARE & DISABILITY SUPPORT WORKER

• Offered services to people with varying disabilities to aid them in achieving desired quality of life, in accordance with rehabilitation, healthcare and support focus plans, and relevant standards

Arranged and supervised activities designed to enhance physical, social and emotional wellbeing.

AIR CHINA, CHENGDU, CHINA, February 2007 - January 2008

AVIATION IMPORT & EXPORT ASSISTANT

- Coordinated orders of aviation materials for all domestic airlines, predominantly parent company Air China
- Cultivated strong relationships with multinational industry leaders including Honeywell, Boeing etc.

EDUCATION AND CREDENTIALS

CERTIFICATE IV OF WEB DESIGN, 2014

Open colleges, Sydney

CERTIFICATE OF FIRST AID, 2011

Australian Red Cross, Hobart

MASTER OF BUSINESS IN INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS, 2009

UTAS Australia, Hobart

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN ENGLISH AND INTERNATIONAL TRADE, 2007 SISU, China

FORKLIFT LICENSE, 2012

Hobart, Tasmania

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages: English, Chinese (bilingual)

Technical Proficiencies: QuickBooks, Microsoft Office Suit, Adobe Web Design Suite

References available upon request